Cut!
Hyesung, your neck
is way too stiff
Okay, I'll try to relax
Okay, let's do it again
Action!
Hwi-rim
All those moments
passed through me
was all you
Cut!
Hyesung, are you
laughing now?
Sorry
One more time
Okay, keep roll
Cut!
How can you
go down like that?
Oh my!
Drink water
and do it again
Action!
Cut!
You've done great so far
What's gotten into you?
This is the last one
Cut!
Ten minutes' break
I'm sorry
Sorry
Are you nervous?
Yes, it's tough
How do you pull it off?
I mean, a kiss scene
Kiss scene…
Can you give me
some useful tips?
As for me
I try to think of him
as someone I like
Someone you like…
The end of my time
always reaches you
It was you
All those moments
passed through me
was all you